Oh my god!
Aah! We're about to kiss!
Huh?
Bestie?
Girl, wake up!
You're acting weird.
You're starting to
dream about him.
So what's the meaning of this?
Nadia, I've found her.
She's kind, but not gentle.
She's Princess Janine.
Princess Janine?
Nadia?
Nadia.
You're awake!
Thank goodness.
Treb, I'm so happy for you!
And because Grandma Nadia
is finally awake,
you can finally
make it up to her.
Did you tell
Grandma Nadia about me?
What?
Oh, about that.
Nadia used to love
my stories about a princess.
Me?
A princess?
Huh?
Well, yeah. It suits you.
A princess who's rough
around the edges.
You're so annoying!
You know, it's because
of my sweet voice
that Grandma Nadia woke up.
Yes. That's definitely
possible.
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE CHIMES]
- "Where are they?"
- "Why haven't they posted?"
[BEEPING]
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
I hope Nadia and I can
still fix things between us.
Yes!
So you can...
...finally move on.
["MULTO" BY
HEALY AFTER DARK PLAYING]
[JAJA] I'll call Bert!
Princess Janine.
[TONY] We've been friends
for five decades now.
But I haven't seen you
like this before.
You put in so much effort
just to make her happy.
["MULTO" CONTINUES]
[EMMA] Girl, this is
something else.
Have you fallen in love
with him already?
["MULTO" CONTINUES]
[EMMA] You're giddy because
you feel something for him.
But that isn't love.
Not yet, at least.
Girl, you might
actually fall for him.
You know how this will end.
["MULTO" CONTINUES]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay.
Girl, let's go!
Girl, aren't you ready?!
It's noon already!
Oh, let's give the siblings
some time alone.
[EMMA] But how? They can't
communicate with each other.
They need a translator,
and that's you, correct?
Mm. You expect Treb
to just stare at her?
-[TONY] Yoo-hoo! Can we come in?
- [QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
They're here.
Okay.
Treb.
Where's Tony?
- Boo!
- Oh!
What's your problem?
Are you crazy?!
What do you mean?
Who's truly crazy here?
[LAUGHS]
Uh, so...
How's Grandma doing?
[DOOR CLOSES]
She's fine.
She's talkative now.
It's like she was
never in a coma.
She laughs with Bert a lot.
Love it!
That's good news,
right, bestie?
Good news. Good news.
[CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY]
That's why we've come
to pick you up.
- Oh, you guys shouldn't have.
- [COUGHS]
[COUGHING]
- Jaja.
- [COUGHING]
- Are you all right?
- Um...
I don't feel well today.
[JAJA CONTINUES COUGHING]
Grandma might catch this cough.
Oh, okay. Emma can just--
- [COUGHING INTENSIFIES]
- I can go.
[COUGHING CONTINUES]
Bestie is asymptomatic.
As you know...
[COUGHS]
You know she stays with me.
She could still be carrying
the virus. [COUGHS]
We just don't know it.
You sound like the MetroCom.
You keep firing!
[IMITATES GUNFIRE]
[EMMA] Wait.
MetroCom? What's that?
[TONY] MetroCom.
They're the police. Cops.
I think you should
sit down, Jaja.
- Take a break.
- Thank you.
Uh, Emma.
Would you mind boiling
some oregano leaves?
And maybe squeeze
some limes too.
- Thank you.
- Uh, thanks for the concern,
but I have some medicine.
[JAJA COUGHS, CLEARS THROAT]
I wish I could
take care of you.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
What are you talking about?
[CLEARS THROAT]
I'm fine.
I think I'll survive.
[COUGHS]
- Bestie?
- Hmm?
I need some water.
[CONTINUES COUGHING]
Girl, it's right
in front of you.
It's been there the whole time.
Mm-hmm. I know.
[CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY]
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[ENGINE REVS]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
One, two, three.
I'll stay here, okay?
I'll keep you company.
It's okay, Treb.
Grandma needs you. [COUGHS]
Grandma needs you
more than I do.
- [JAJA COUGHS]
- She's fine now.
Her condition has improved.
I'll just stay here
and keep an eye on you.
It's okay, Treb, I promise.
Uh, but if you want
to stay here...
...that's okay, too.
[CLEARS THROAT]
I keep looking for your voice.
[THUDS] Really?
Uh, yes.
- It's soothing.
- Oh.
And Nadia keeps looking
for your voice.
She keeps talking about
hearing a woman's voice.
So we decided to
fetch you and Emma.
I hope you get
to talk to her already.
That way, I can communicate
with my sister.
Is that so? Why didn't you
tell me right away?
Because I was worried
about your cough.
I'm going to get dressed now.
- We'll go there now.
- Wow! [EMMA CLAPS]
It's a miracle!
Your cough is gone already?
You sounded like Susan Africa
with all your coughing earlier.
Praise the Lord!
It's a miracle!
Praise the Lord
for I am healed!
Amen.
You can cure coughs
instantly now?
- That's awesome!
- Mm-hmm.
You know, you guys
should go ahead.
Jaja and I will follow, okay?
She just needs to rest a bit,
but I think she'll be
better soon.
Up to you.
- Yes.
- Okay.
Thank you. Bye, guys.
Are we leaving?
I was about to
perfect that dance.
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[COUGHS]
You said you weren't
in love with him.
- I thought so too, bestie.
- Bestie...
He's just different from Vhal.
[SIGHS] I was all over the place
when I was with Vhal.
I kept chasing him.
But with Wilberto,
it's different.
[JAJA] It feels like...
...I don't need to
chase after him.
I feel relaxed and chill.
[JAJA] That's how I feel.
Oh, come on.
Bestie, it's not my fault
that I have feelings
for a ghost.
- Tsk.
- I've moved on from Vhal.
[SIGHS] Girl.
We opened your third eye,
not your heart.
Can't you close your heart?
It's not good for you. Tsk.
I don't want him to go.
When he fixes things
with Grandma Nadia,
we won't see
each other again, bestie.
Oh.
So that's why you were
pretending to have a cough.
It's just a delaying tactic.
But I promised him
that I would help him
and Grandma Nadia.
[SIGHS] And I don't plan on
breaking that promise.
When that happens,
I'll be happy for them.
[JAJA] I'll go get ready.
They might be waiting for us.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Good afternoon.
That's the voice I heard.
I'm sorry I let her in--
I want to get to know her.
Hello, Grandma.
You can call me Jaja.
My real name is Janine.
Princess Janine.
I also heard a man's voice.
Was that my brother, Wilberto?
It's been ages since
we last saw each other.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Many people have tried
connecting my brother and I.
[LABORED BREATHING]
Maybe it's better he never
saw where I ended up.
Since we lost our parents...
[NADIA]
...he changed.
Nadia.
Stay here, okay?
Take care of yourself.
Can I come with you, Wilberto?
You can't.
But, Wilberto, I don't
want to be alone.
Can you tell me the story
about the princess?
It's getting dark.
I need to find us some food.
I'll help you.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
Cut it out, Nadia .
Stop being a burden.
[NADIA]
He lost his temper often.
He became very strict.
I felt like he loved our country
more than he loved me.
Just stay here, okay?
Don't go out.
I left you some food.
I'm scared
you'll leave me, Wilberto.
I promise
I'll come back for you.
- [SMOOCHES]
- [SNIFFLES]
I'll be back.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
WIlberto?
Wilberto?
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
[NADIA]
I waited, and I waited...
Until the days
turned into weeks.
[COUGHING]
I felt like he
abandoned me because...
Because I was a burden to him.
I told myself that I was
going to fight for my life.
I am not a burden.
I never became
a burden to anyone.
I didn't mean to do that.
I was angry back then.
I didn't realize that you were
hurt by my actions and words.
He says that
he didn't mean to do that.
He was just angry back then.
That's why he said
those harsh words.
He was guilty.
Aren't you a translator?
Why are you defending him?
I experienced something
similar to you, Grandma.
I have also been left behind
and abandoned.
Mm? Then shouldn't we
be on the same side?
Grandma, what differs
in our situations is that...
The person who
left you is... here now.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Tell her that
I won't give up on her.
He says that he won't give up
until he earns your forgiveness.
I have very little time left
in this world.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
He says he has very
little time left in this world.
Are we going to waste
that time left?
Let's do what we have to do,
and say what we have to say.
I love you.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
You love them.
Huh? Uh... Who?
- You.
- Her.
Uh... Yes, Grandma.
He loves you so much.
He is here to ask
for your forgiveness.
I just wanted to protect you,
so I joined the guerrillas.
But I didn't know that I would
never be able to come back.
He wanted to protect you,
that's why he joined
the guerrillas.
And that's where he was killed.
That's why he couldn't
come back to you.
Other people have told me
about Wilberto's presence,
but I always ignored it.
I had to almost die
before I listened to him.
It's all right, Grandma.
You were hurt.
What matters
is that you're here.
[SOBBING]
Wilberto...
[SNIFFLES] Wilberto, I don't
want us angry at each other.
Wilberto, I forgive you.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [VEHICLES RUMBLING]
- [HORNS HONKING]
I know that he's going
to leave soon, bestie, but...
It's still too painful for me.
Why am I so weak?
What's wrong?
["PAUWI NA AKO"
BY GAB PLAYING]
Baby!
["PAUWI NA AKO" CONTINUES]
So, are you excited
to enter heaven?
Bro?
Don't leave yet.
- What?
- Don't go...
I'll be right here, Jaja.
- Vhal...
- Vhal?!
What's this guy doing here?
Oh, wow...
I dare you to hurt Jaja again.
Bro, he's getting scared.
Come on, let's go.
He's about to bolt, man.
Just leave her alone!
Tell me you want
to get back with him.
- Jaja.
- Come out here.
Stop it!
Could you two stop this?!
Can you please not make this
any more complicated?!
Jaja...
[ELECTRICITY SPARKING]
Jaja!